Anyone who disobeys
will be executed immediately.
We accept!
We accept everything!
David, Jack, come here.
Their castles, carriages, jewels, gold,
take whatever you want.
Severin,
I mean, Godfather, is this real?
Just call me Severin.
Of course it’s real.
I told you I could make
you anything you wanted to be.
I keep my word.
- Thank you, Severin!
This is Elowen Morellan, heir of
the Morellan family,
and my wife.
I expect all of
you to support her
and the Morellan
family from now on.
Severin… are you truly the Godfather?
Yes.
My Lady!
Oh God!
Cassia, protect my mother.
Elowen, come with me.
What’s wrong?
The Black Dragon
Covenant issued an ultimatum.
Twelve hours.
If we don't comply, the
Four Great Families are done.
What do they want?
Submit to them and
supply endless energy crystals.
So the proposal
was just a cover.
You really came for help.
The help I need is real.
But my feelings are more real.
I fell in love
with you
the day you destroyed the Skeleton Legion
and founded the Sovereign Sanctum.
Don't worry. I'll handle this.
I trust you.
They have undying knights,
but my father says you
can save all of Golantis.
Your father is right.
The Black Dragon Covenant may be
powerful,
but to me they’re nothing.
I’ll contact the Black Dragon right now
through the Void Realm.